Are there any free cosmetics for L'Oréal employees?
We have so many free products
I haven't bought any products from L'Oréal
since I started my job
Today, we are going to interview
the L'Oréal office in Taiwan
Our office was renovated in 2002
There is a product wall here
If you are going on a date
but you forget to spray your perfume
the staff will come here to spray it
We also have our own cafe
There is also some salty food
such as beef noodles and dumplings
My favorite is our fruit box
What are the benefits of working at L'Oréal?
The working environment is free
You can work from home for a certain period of time every week
So I hope everyone can apply for this year's
2024 CITS Reserve Staff Plan before March 3